Guillermo Cerame

I'm finishing my web development studies after having worked as a live audio engineer for the last 8 years. Over this period I developed my communication, problem solving and team working skills. I enjoy learning about new technologies, languages or frameworks and I'm interested in all aspects of web development.

EDUCATION

CFGS Desarrollo de Aplicaciones Web

IES Tetuán de las Victorias

Sept 2021 - Present - 2 years, Madrid

Java, PHP, Javascript, MySQL, HTML/CSS, Bash and Powershell scripting.

Node, Express, React, NextJS

Online courses and self taught

2021 - Present

Followed various online courses and resources to learn these technologies and developed small projects using them.

- Modern Javascript Bootcamp Course (Colt Steele, Udemy) 52h
- Learn React (Scrimba) 12h.
- Java Developer (Jetbrains Academy) 150h

BA in Audio Production

Middlesex University

2013-2015 Madrid and Amsterdam

Graduated with first class honors.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Audio Engineer

2014 - 2020, Amsterdam and Randstad area

2020 - Present, Madrid

Worked as a freelance audio engineer in many different environments, from corporate events to electronic music festivals in the Amsterdam area. Also have experience in film shoots and post-production. g.cerame@gmail.com +34 648230487 github.com/gcerame

Skills

Backend development Frontend development Live audio, postproduction and studio recording

Tools & Technologies

Javascript, PHP, Java, Relational and Nonrelational Databases

Other Skills

HTML, CSS, Git, Testing

Languages

Spanish (native) English (C2) German (B2) Dutch(B1)